Guide to the Images of Yale Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Alphabetical List of Individuals, Series I
  - Smith, David (Box 62, Folder 2349)
  - Smith, David M. (Box 62, Folder 2349)
  - Smith, David Page (Box 62, Folder 2349)
  - Smith, David Stanley (Box 62, Folder 2349)
  - Smith, E. L. (Box 62, Folder 2350)
  - Smith, Earl (Box 62, Folder 2351)
  - Smith, Edson(?) (Box 62, Folder 2351)
  - Smith, Edward Fairchild (Box 62, Folder 2351)
  - Smith, Edwin Burritt (Box 62, Folder 2351)
  - Smith, Elliot Dunlap (Box 62, Folder 2352)
  - Smith, Ernest Ellsworth (Box 62, Folder 2353)
  - Smith, Everett (Box 62, Folder 2353)
  - Smith, F. Hopkinson (Box 62, Folder 2353)
  - Smith, Floyd R. (Box 62, Folder 2353)
  - Smith, Fred (Box 62, Folder 2354)
  - Smith, George Fairlamb (Box 62, Folder 2354)
  - Smith, George H. E. (Box 62, Folder 2355)
  - Smith, George Milton (Box 62, Folder 2355)
  - Smith, H. A. (Box 62, Folder 2356)
  - Smith, Harold V. (Box 62, Folder 2356)
  - Smith, Henry DeWitt (Box 62, Folder 2356)
  - Smith, Herbert Augustine (Box 62, Folder 2356)
  - Smith, Herbert E. (Box 62, Folder 2356)
  - Smith, Horatio E. (Box 62, Folder 2357)
  - Smith, Irving Wright (Box 62, Folder 2357)
  - Smith, Isaac (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box 62, Folder 2357)
  - Smith, J. Joseph (Box 62, Folder 2358)
  - Smith, James W. (YC 1873) (Box 62, Folder 2358)
  - Smith, James G. (Box 62, Folder 2358)
  - Smith, Joel Sumner (Box 62, Folder 2358)
  - Smith, John Cotton (Box 62, Folder 2358)
  - Smith, L. R. (Box 62, Folder 2359)
  - Smith, Lloyd Waddell (Box 62, Folder 2359)
  - Smith, Moses (Box 62, Folder 2359)
  - Smith, Nathan (Box 63, Folder 2360)
  - Smith, Nathaniel (Box 63, Folder 2361)
  - Smith, Noah (Box 63, Folder 2361)
  - Smith, Normand (Box 63, Folder 2361)
  - Smith, Old Pop (Box 63, Folder 2362)
  - Smith, Palmer (Box 63, Folder 2362)
  - Smith, Percy Franklyn (Box 63, Folder 2362)
  - Smith, Robert Seneca (Box 63, Folder 2362)
  - Smith, Rufus Biggs (Box 63, Folder 2362)
  - Smith, Sidney Irving (Box 63, Folder 2363)
  - Smith, Sumner (Box 63, Folder 2364)
  - Smith, Truman (Box 63, Folder 2364)
  - Smith, W.L. (Box 63, Folder 2364)
  - Smith, W. W. (Box 63, Folder 2365)
  - Smith, Walker (Box 63, Folder 2365)
  - Smith, Walter B. (Box 63, Folder 2365)
  - Smith, Walton Hall (Box 63, Folder 2365)
  - Smith, Wilder (Box 63, Folder 2365)
  - Smith, William (Box 63, Folder 2366)
  - Smith, William C. (Box 63, Folder 2366)
  - Smith, William H. (Box 63, Folder 2366)
  - Smith, William Manlius (Box 63, Folder 2367)
  - Smith, Wint (Box 63, Folder 2367)
  - Smyth, Rev. Newman (Box 63, Folder 2368)
  - Smyth, Walter H. (Box 63, Folder 2368)
  - Smythe, H. B. (Box 63, Folder 2368)
  - Sneath, E. Hershey (Box 63, Folder 2369)
  - Snell, Thomas Cullen Bryant (Box 63, Folder 2369)
  - Snow, Rev. Frederic Elkanah (Box 63, Folder 2369)
  - Snowden, George H. (Box 63, Folder 2370)
  - Snowden, Col. John B. (Box 63, Folder 2371)
  - Solomon, Joseph (Box 63, Folder 2371)
  - Somers, Edward J. (Box 63, Folder 2371)
  - Soule, Walter (Box 63, Folder 2371)
  - Southard, George Henry (Box 63, Folder 2372)
  - Souther, John Ira (Box 63, Folder 2372)
  - Souther, William T. (YC 1873) (Box 63, Folder 2372)
  - Southey, Charles Richard (Box 63, Folder 2372)
  - Southgate, Stuart L. (Box 63, Folder 2373)
  - Southworth, George Champlain Shepard (Box 63, Folder 2373)
  - Spain, August O. (Box 63, Folder 2373)
  - Spalding, E. S. (Box 63, Folder 2374)
  - Spalding, George Atherton (Box 63, Folder 2374)
  - Spalding, George Brown (Box 63, Folder 2374)
  - Spalding, Rufus P. (Box 63, Folder 2375)
  - Spang, Kenneth M. (Box 63, Folder 2375)
  - Spanier, Emil (Box 63, Folder 2375)
  - Sparrowe, Lewis Edwards (Box 63, Folder 2376)
  - Spaulding, Albert Tenney (Box 63, Folder 2376)
  - Spaulding, Frank E. (Box 63, Folder 2377)
  - Spaulding, George B. (Box 63, Folder 2377)
  - Spence, T. H. (Box 63, Folder 2378)
  - Spencer, Dumausq(?) (Box 63, Folder 2378)
  - Spencer, Edward Curran (Box 63, Folder 2378)
  - Spencer, Edward L. (Box 63, Folder 2379)
  - Spencer, Frank O. (Box 63, Folder 2379)
  - Spencer, Israel Selden (Box 63, Folder 2379)
  - Spencer, Llewellyn T. (Box 63, Folder 2380)
  - Spencer, Oliver Wade (Box 63, Folder 2380)
  - Spencer, Samuel Reid (Box 63, Folder 2380)
  - Spencer, Selden P. (Box 63, Folder 2381)
  - Spencer, Seldon Palmer (Box 63, Folder 2381)
  - Sperling, Jerome (Box 63, Folder 2381)
  - Sperry, Frederick N. (Box 63, Folder 2382)
  - Sperry, George Thorncliffe (Box 63, Folder 2382)
  - Sperry, Rev. Willard L. (Box 63, Folder 2382)
  - Speranza, Carlo Leonardo (Box 63, Folder 2383)
  - Spitzer, Lyman (Box 63, Folder 2384)
  - Splayyn, William W. M. (Box 63, Folder 2384)
  - Spock, Dr. Benjamin (Box 63, Folder 2385)
  - Spooner, John C. (Box 63, Folder 2386)
  - Spooner, Samuel Brigham (Box 63, Folder 2387)
  - Spottswood, Curran L., Jr. (Box 63, Folder 2387)
  - Sprague, Mrs. A. A. (Box 63, Folder 2388)
  - Sprague, Frank E. (YC 1873) (Box 63, Folder 2388)
  - Sprague, Homer Baxter (Box 63, Folder 2388)
  - Sprague, Paul W. (Box 63, Folder 2388)
  - Sprague, Rev. William Buell (Box 63, Folder 2389)
  - Sprague, William C. (Box 63, Folder 2389)
  - Spring, Andrew Jackson (Box 63, Folder 2390)
  - Spring, Gardiner (Box 63, Folder 2390)
  - Spring, Samuel N. (Box 63, Folder 2390)
  - Sproat, James (Box 63, Folder 2391)
  - Spurr, Arthur C. (Box 63, Folder 2391)
  - Spykman, Nicholas J. (Box 63, Folder 2391)
  - Squire, Allan Taft (Box 63, Folder 2392)
  - Squire, Roger W. (Box 63, Folder 2392)
  - Stabler (Box 63, Folder 2393)
  - Stabler, Charles Miller (Box 63, Folder 2393)
  - Stack, Henry Levi (Box 63, Folder 2393)
  - Stack, Joseph William (Box 63, Folder 2393)
  - Stagg, Amos Alonzo (Box 63, Folder 2394)
  - Stahl, Daisy (Box 63, Folder 2395)
  - Staley, Allen C. (Box 63, Folder 2395)
  - Stanley, Anthony D. (Box 63, Folder 2396)
  - Stanley, Clarence D. (Box 63, Folder 2397)
  - Stanley, Hannibal Lowe (Box 63, Folder 2397)
  - Stanley, Michael (Box 63, Folder 2397)
  - Stanley, Oran B. (Box 63, Folder 2398)
  - Stanley, William (Box 63, Folder 2398)
  - Stanton, Charles Thompson (Box 63, Folder 2398)
  - Stanton, Lewis N. (Box 63, Folder 2399)
  - Stapler, Henry Beidleman Bascon (Box 63, Folder 2399)
  - Starr, Edward Comfort (Box 63, Folder 2400)
  - Starr, Grosvenor (Box 63, Folder 2400)
  - Starr, Pierre Sythoff (Box 63, Folder 2400)
  - Starkweather, George Pratt (Box 63, Folder 2401)
  - Starling, Charles Hensley (Box 63, Folder 2401)
  - Starret, John William (Box 63, Folder 2402)
  - Stearns, Charles Cummings (Box 63, Folder 2402)
  - Stearns, Elliot (Box 63, Folder 2402)
  - Stearns, Harold Cranford (Box 63, Folder 2403)
  - Stearns, Henry P. (Box 63, Folder 2403)
  - Stearns, Thomas Calhoun (Box 63, Folder 2403)
  - Stebbins, Henry H. (Box 64, Folder 2404)
  - Stebbins, Henry Hamlin (Box 64, Folder 2404)
  - Stebbins, Walter G. (Box 64, Folder 2404)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence (Box 64, Folder 2405)
  - Steele, Porter (Box 64, Folder 2406)
  - Steele, Thomas C. (Box 64, Folder 2406)
  - Steele, William Henry (Box 64, Folder 2406)
  - Steffen, Roscoe Turner (Box 64, Folder 2406)
  - Steiner, Harold A. (Box 64, Folder 2407)
  - Stephens, Ferris J. (Box 64, Folder 2407)
  - Stephenson, Charles Sing (Box 64, Folder 2407)
  - Stephenson, Frank Bryan (Box 64, Folder 2408)
  - Sterling, Edward (Box 64, Folder 2408)
  - Sterling, Francis N. (Box 64, Folder 2408)
  - Sterling, George Loomis (Box 64, Folder 2408)
  - Sterling, John William (Box 64, Folder 2409-14)
  - Stern, Robert B. (Box 64, Folder 2415)
  - Stern, Robert A. M. (Box 64, Folder 2415)
  - Stevens, Alexander Henry (Box 64, Folder 2416)
  - Stevens, Carleton Hickock (Box 64, Folder 2416)
  - Stevens, Clement D. (Box 64, Folder 2416)
  - Stevens, Earl (Box 64, Folder 2417)
  - Stevens, Edward S. (Box 64, Folder 2417)
  - Stevens, Frederic William (Box 64, Folder 2417)
  - Stevens, George Barker (Prof.) (Box 64, Folder 2418)
  - Stevens, Guy Ernest (Box 64, Folder 2419)
  - Stevens, Henry (Box 64, Folder 2419)
  - Stevens, Jerald L. (Box 64, Folder 2419)
  - Stevens, Joseph (Box 64, Folder 2419)
  - Stevens, Marvin Allen (Box 64, Folder 2420)
  - Stevens, Robert Ten Broeck (Box 64, Folder 2420)
  - Stevens, Shepherd (Box 64, Folder 2420)
  - Stevenson, Robert III (Box 64, Folder 2421)
  - Stevenson, Robert E. (Box 64, Folder 2421)
  - Stewart, [?] (Box 64, Folder 2421)
  - Stewart, Charles (Box 64, Folder 2422)
  - Stewart, Donald Ogden (Box 64, Folder 2422)
  - Stewart, Captain George (Box 64, Folder 2422)
  - Stewart, J. T. III (Box 64, Folder 2423)
  - Stewart, John Muirhead (Box 64, Folder 2423)
  - Stewart, Lispenard (Box 64, Folder 2423)
  - Stewart, Philip B. (Box 64, Folder 2424)
  - Stewart, Potter (Box 64, Folder 2424)
  - Stewart, Seth T. (Box 64, Folder 2425)
  - Stewart, Hon. William Morris (Box 64, Folder 2425)
  - Stickman, Herman T. (Box 64, Folder 2426)
  - Stickney, George Fetter (Box 64, Folder 2426)
  - Stiles, Carrington Riverius (Box 64, Folder 2426)
  - Stiles, Edgar (Box 64, Folder 2426)
  - Stiles, Ezra (Box 64, Folder 2427-28)
    - Portraits, engravings & drawings (Box 64, Folder 2427-28)
    - Related photos of graves, coat of arms and portraits of children (Box 64, Folder 2429-30)
  - Stiles, Robert A. (Box 64, Folder 2431)
  - Stiles, William A. (Box 64, Folder 2431)
  - Stille, Charles Janeway (Box 64, Folder 2431)
  - Stillman, Francis Hill (Box 64, Folder 2432)
  - Stillman, Philip Tracy (Box 64, Folder 2432)
  - Stimson, Frederick Julian (Box 64, Folder 2432)
  - Stimson [?] (Box 64, Folder 2433)
  - Stimson, Henry L. (Box 64, Folder 2433)
  - Stimson, Lewis A. (Box 64, Folder 2433)
  - Stinespring, William F. (Box 64, Folder 2434)
  - Stirling, Sir Walter (Box 64, Folder 2434)
  - Stocker, James D. (Box 64, Folder 2434)
  - Stocking, Gilbert Miles (Box 64, Folder 2435)
  - Stoddard, David Tappan (Box 64, Folder 2435)
  - Stoddard, L. L. (Box 64, Folder 2435)
  - Stoddard, L. R. (Box 64, Folder 2436)
  - Stoddard, Louis Ezekiel (Box 64, Folder 2436)
  - Stoddart, John C. (Box 64, Folder 2436)
  - Stoddart, John Thomas (Box 64, Folder 2436)
  - Stoeckel, Gustave Jacob (Box 65, Folder 2437)
  - Stoeckel, Robbins Battell (Box 65, Folder 2438)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps (Box 65, Folder 2439)
  - Stokes, Walter (Box 65, Folder 2439)
  - Stokes, William Earl Dodge (Box 65, Folder 2439)
  - Stone, Edward C. (Box 65, Folder 2440)
  - Stone, Edward Durell (Box 65, Folder 2440)
  - Stone, Harlan Fiske (Box 65, Folder 2440)
  - Stone, J. Herbert (Box 65, Folder 2440)
  - Stone, Louis Talcott, Jr. (Box 65, Folder 2441)
  - Stone, Leon S. (Box 65, Folder 2441)
  - Stone, Philip Avery (Box 65, Folder 2441)
  - Stone, Robert Edward (Box 65, Folder 2442)
  - Stoner, James L. (Box 65, Folder 2442)
  - Storr, Lewis A. (Box 65, Folder 2442)
  - Stoner, Frank(?) (Box 65, Folder 2443)
  - Storrs, Melancthon (Box 65, Folder 2444)
  - Storrs, William Lucius (Box 65, Folder 2444)
  - Stott, Robert Doulton (Box 65, Folder 2445)
  - Stoughton, Bradley (Box 65, Folder 2445)
  - Stow, Frederick Enos (Box 65, Folder 2445)
  - Stowell, Alexander David (Box 65, Folder 2446)
  - Strathcona, Lord (Smith, Donald A.) (Box 65, Folder 2446)
  - Strauss, William M. (Box 65, Folder 2447)
  - Street, Augustus Russell, Mr. & Mrs. (Box 65, Folder 2448)
  - Street, George Edward (Box 65, Folder 2449)
  - Street, Henry A. (Box 65, Folder 2449)
  - Street, Titus (Box 65, Folder 2449)
  - Strickland, Dr. Harold (Box 65, Folder 2449)
  - Strong, Augustus Hopkins (Box 65, Folder 2450)
  - Strong, George Washington (Box 65, Folder 2451)
  - Strong, Henry (Box 65, Folder 2451)
  - Strong, Nathan (Box 65, Folder 2451)
  - Strong, Nehemiah (Box 65, Folder 2452)
  - Strong, Nelson Hooker (Box 65, Folder 2452)
  - Strong, Otis (Box 65, Folder 2452)
  - Strong, Selan Brewster (1811) (Box 65, Folder 2453)
  - Strong, Selan Brewster (1864) (Box 65, Folder 2453)
  - Strong, Theodore (1812) (Box 65, Folder 2453)
  - Strong, Theodore (1914) (Box 65, Folder 2453)
  - Strong, Ullman (YC 1873) (Box 65, Folder 2453)
  - Strong, William (Box 65, Folder 2454)
  - Strong, William Thaddeus (Box 65, Folder 2454)
  - Strout, Edwin A. (Box 65, Folder 2454)
  - Studley, John Payne (Box 65, Folder 2455)
  - Sturm, Justin Cornelius (Box 65, Folder 2455)
  - Sturm, Paul (Box 65, Folder 2456)
  - Sturges, Hezeniah (Box 65, Folder 2456)
  - Sturges, Wesley Alba (Box 65, Folder 2456)
  - Sturtevant, Albert Dillon (Box 65, Folder 2457)
  - Sturtevant, Charles (Box 65, Folder 2457)
  - Sturtevant, Edgar H. (Box 65, Folder 2458)
  - Sturtevant, J. M. (Box 65, Folder 2458)
  - Suder, Louis (Box 65, Folder 2459)
  - Suffren, Charles (Box 65, Folder 2459)
  - Suisman, E. A. (Box 65, Folder 2459)
  - Sullivan, Harold W. (Box 65, Folder 2460)
  - Sullivan, Robert J. (Box 65, Folder 2460)
  - Sumner, Charles B. (Box 65, Folder 2460)
  - Sumner, Charles E. (Box 65, Folder 2461)
  - Sumner, Graham (Box 65, Folder 2461)
  - Sumner, William Graham (Box 65, Folder 2462)
  - Sundgaard, Arnold (Box 65, Folder 2463)
  - Sutherland, Richard (Box 65, Folder 2463)
  - Sutphin, Stuart B. (Box 65, Folder 2463)
  - Sutro, Ogden W. (Box 65, Folder 2463)
  - Suttie, Roscoe Henry (Box 65, Folder 2464)
  - Sutton, Edward Owen (Box 65, Folder 2464)
  - Swalbacher, Norton (Box 65, Folder 2464)
  - Swan, Thomas W. (Box 65, Folder 2465)
  - Swartwout, Egerton (Box 65, Folder 2465)
  - Swayne, Wager (Box 65, Folder 2465)
  - Swazey, Albert D. (Box 65, Folder 2466)
  - Sweet, D. S. (Box 65, Folder 2466)
  - Sweet, Preston Irving (Box 65, Folder 2466)
  - Sweet, Stanley Adams (Box 65, Folder 2466)
  - Sweetser, Henry E. (Box 65, Folder 2467)
  - Sweetser, Jess William (Box 65, Folder 2467)
  - Swenson, Svante Magnus (Box 65, Folder 2467)
  - Swift, Frederick Booth (Box 65, Folder 2468)
  - Swisher, Charles Clinton (Box 65, Folder 2468)
  - Switzer, St. Clair A. (Box 65, Folder 2468)
  - Sykes, Dorson (Box 65, Folder 2469)
  - Symington, William H. (Box 65, Folder 2469)
  - Symington, William Stuart (Box 65, Folder 2469)
  - Taber, John (Box 65, Folder 2470)
  - Taft, Alphonso (Box 66, Folder 2471)
  - Taft, Charles Phelps (1864) (Box 66, Folder 2471)
  - Taft, Charles Phelps (1918) (Box 66, Folder 2471)
  - Taft, Edmund M. (Box 66, Folder 2472)
  - Taft, Henry Waters (Box 66, Folder 2472)
  - Taft, Hora (Box 66, Folder 2472)
  - Taft, Horace Dutton (Box 66, Folder 2472)
  - Taft, Robert Alphonso (Box 66, Folder 2473)
  - Taft, William Howard (Box 66, Folder 2474-84)
  - Taintor, James U. (Box 66, Folder 2485)
  - Tajiri, Inajiro (Box 66, Folder 2485)
  - Talbott, Harold E. (Box 66, Folder 2485)
  - Talbott, N. S. (Box 66, Folder 2486)
  - Talcott, Charles H. (Box 66, Folder 2486)
  - Talcott, George (Box 66, Folder 2486)
  - Talcott, J. C. (Box 66, Folder 2487)
  - Talcott, John Butler (Box 66, Folder 2487)
  - Talcott, Samuel (Box 66, Folder 2487)
  - Talmadge, Benjamin (Box 66, Folder 2488)
  - Tanimura, Issa (Box 66, Folder 2488)
  - Tanis, James Robert (Box 66, Folder 2488)
  - Tanner, Allen P. (Box 66, Folder 2488)
  - Tarbell, Frank B. (Box 66, Folder 2489)
  - Tarbox, Luther G. (Box 66, Folder 2489)
  - Taylor, Alfred J. (Box 66, Folder 2489)
  - Taylor, Archibald (Box 66, Folder 2490)
  - Taylor, Charles H. (Box 66, Folder 2490)
  - Taylor, Donald W. (Box 66, Folder 2490)
  - Taylor, Edwin Cassius (Box 66, Folder 2490)
  - Taylor, Effie (Box 66, Folder 2491)
  - Taylor, George Burton (Box 66, Folder 2491)
  - Taylor, George F. (Box 66, Folder 2491)
  - Taylor, John C. (Box 66, Folder 2492)
  - Taylor, John P. (Box 66, Folder 2492)
  - Taylor, Lewis Pinney (Box 66, Folder 2492)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel William (Box 66, Folder 2493)
  - Taylor, William Ambrose (Box 66, Folder 2494)
  - Taylor, William Henry (Box 66, Folder 2494)
  - Taylor, William Hovell (Box 66, Folder 2494)
  - Teasdale, Sarah (Box 67, Folder 2495)
  - Tedeschi, Cosmo (Box 67, Folder 2496)
  - Telford, Worthington S. (Box 67, Folder 2497)
  - Ten Eyck, Henry James (Box 67, Folder 2497)
  - Tenney, Daniel Gleason (Box 67, Folder 2497)
  - Tenney, Levi S. (Box 67, Folder 2498)
  - Terry, Adrian (Box 67, Folder 2498)
  - Terry, Alfred Howe (Box 67, Folder 2498)
  - Terry, Frank S. (Box 67, Folder 2499)
  - Terry, George Davis (Box 67, Folder 2499)
  - Terry, James (Box 67, Folder 2499)
  - Thacher, Edward Stanley (Box 67, Folder 2500)
  - Thacher, James Kingsley (Box 67, Folder 2500)
  - Thacher, John Seymour (Box 67, Folder 2501)
  - Thacher, Thomas Anthony (Box 67, Folder 2502-05)
  - Thacher, Thomas Day (Box 67, Folder 2506)
  - Thacher, William Larned (Box 67, Folder 2507)
  - Thalheimer (Box 67, Folder 2508)
  - Thanhouser, Lloyd F. (Box 67, Folder 2508)
  - Thayer, Henry W. (Box 67, Folder 2508)
  - Thayer, John R. (Box 67, Folder 2509)
  - Thayer, Reuel Harvey, Jr. (Box 67, Folder 2509)
  - Thomas, Antoine (Box 67, Folder 2510)
  - Thomas, Charles Henry (Box 67, Folder 2510)
  - Thomas, Charles Lloyd (Box 67, Folder 2511)
  - Thomas, Elisha Smith (Box 67, Folder 2511)
  - Thomas, Frederick Folger (Box 67, Folder 2512)
  - Thomas, H. C. (Box 67, Folder 2512)
  - Thomas, J. P. (Box 67, Folder 2512)
  - Thomas, John Green (Box 67, Folder 2513)
  - Thomas, John H. (Box 67, Folder 2513)
  - Thomas, Joseph B. (Box 67, Folder 2513)
  - Thomas, Lewis (Box 67, Folder 2514)
  - Thomas, Nathaniel Philip Smith (Box 67, Folder 2514)
  - Thomas, Ralph Willis & Grandparents (Thomas, Mr & Mrs. George H.) (Box 67, Folder 2514)
  - Thomas, Richard Banks (Box 67, Folder 2515)
  - Thomas, Viola Malkin (Box 67, Folder 2515)
  - Thomas, Virginia Carrington (Box 67, Folder 2515)
  - Thomasson, E. M. (Box 67, Folder 2516)
  - Thompson, Arthur (Box 67, Folder 2516)
  - Thompson, Colin (Box 67, Folder 2516)
  - Thompson, Dorothy (Box 67, Folder 2516)
  - Thompson, Edwin Potter (Box 67, Folder 2517)
  - Thompson, George Edwin, Jr. (Box 67, Folder 2518)
  - Thompson, Heber Samuel (Box 67, Folder 2518)
  - Thompson, Joseph Parrish (Box 67, Folder 2518)
  - Thompson, Norman Frederick (Box 67, Folder 2519)
  - Thompson, William H. (Box 67, Folder 2519)
  - Thomson, A. C. (Box 67, Folder 2520)
  - Thomson, Keith S. (Box 67, Folder 2520)
  - Thomson, Samuel Clifton (Box 67, Folder 2521)
  - Thorn, Charles Edwin (Box 67, Folder 2521)
  - Thornberry, John (Box 67, Folder 2521)
  - Thorne, Samuel Brickenhoff (Box 67, Folder 2521)
  - Thorne, Samuel Edmund (Box 67, Folder 2522)
  - Thorne, William V. S. (Box 67, Folder 2522)
  - Thornton, Ollie (Box 67, Folder 2523)
  - Thorpe, Malcolm Rutherford (Box 67, Folder 2523)
  - Thorpe, Warren (Box 67, Folder 2524)
  - Thrall, George Sanford (Box 67, Folder 2524)
  - Throckmorton, Samuel R. (Box 67, Folder 2524)
  - Thurston, Edward Sampson (Box 67, Folder 2524)
  - Thurston, John Lawrence (Box 67, Folder 2525)
  - Thurston, L. P. (Box 67, Folder 2525)
  - Thurston, Thomas G. (Box 67, Folder 2526)
  - Tibbs, Brooke (Box 67, Folder 2526)
  - Tien yow, Jeme (Box 67, Folder 2526)
  - Tierman, George (Box 67, Folder 2527)
  - Tierman, H. D. (Box 67, Folder 2527)
  - Tift, Thomas W. (Box 67, Folder 2527)
  - Tighe, Ambrose (Box 67, Folder 2527)
  - Tighe, Laurence G. (Box 67, Folder 2528)
  - Tigre, C. (Box 67, Folder 2528)
  - Tilden, Charles Joseph (Box 67, Folder 2528)
  - Tilden, Samuel J. (Box 67, Folder 2529)
  - Tilney, Albert Arthur (Box 67, Folder 2529)
  - Tilney, Robert Fingland (Box 67, Folder 2530)
  - Tilson, John Quillin (Box 67, Folder 2531)
  - Timlow, Herman R. (Box 67, Folder 2532)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster (Box 67, Folder 2533)
  - Titus, Ormrod Scandy (Box 67, Folder 2534)
  - Tjader, Richard (Box 67, Folder 2534)
  - Tobey, S. H. (Box 67, Folder 2534)
  - Todd, Edwin S. (Box 67, Folder 2535)
  - Todd, Eli (Box 67, Folder 2535)
  - Todd, Francis Harrison (Box 67, Folder 2535)
  - Todd, John Edwards (Box 67, Folder 2536)
  - Todd, L. E. (Box 67, Folder 2536)
  - Tolles, B. F. (Box 67, Folder 2536)
  - Tolles, King (Box 67, Folder 2537)
  - Tolson, Benjamin Franklin (Box 67, Folder 2537)
  - Tomei, Peter Andrew (Box 67, Folder 2537)
  - Tomkins, Stirling (Box 68, Folder 2538)
  - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 68, Folder 2538)
  - Tomlinson, Daniel G. (Box 68, Folder 2538)
  - Tomlinson, Joseph (Box 68, Folder 2538)
  - Tompkins, Ray (Box 68, Folder 2539)
  - Tong, Kwon Oh [Tsai Shou Kie] (Box 68, Folder 2540)
  - Tookey, Norman Edward (Box 68, Folder 2540)
  - Tooker, Lewis Frank (Box 68, Folder 2540)
  - Torbert, James Rockwell (Box 68, Folder 2541)
  - Torrance, Jared Sidney (Box 68, Folder 2541)
  - Torrey, Charles Cutler (Box 68, Folder 2541)
  - Torrey, Reuben Archer (Box 68, Folder 2542)
  - Totman, David Maydole (Box 68, Folder 2542)
  - Tourney, James William (Box 68, Folder 2542)
  - Tower, Charlemagne, Jr. (Box 68, Folder 2543)
  - Towle, Charles Stewart (Box 68, Folder 2543)
  - Towle, George Makepeace (Box 68, Folder 2543)
  - Town, Ithiel (Box 68, Folder 2544)
  - Townsend, Charles (Box 68, Folder 2544)
  - Townsend, Edward H. (Box 68, Folder 2544)
  - Townsend, Isaac Henry (Box 68, Folder 2545)
  - Townsend, Richard Rodermond (Box 68, Folder 2545)
  - Townsend, Robert Donaldson (Box 68, Folder 2545)
  - Townsend, William Knecland (Box 68, Folder 2546)
  - Tracey, Joshua (Box 68, Folder 2546)
  - Tracy, John Clayton (Box 68, Folder 2547)
  - Tracy, Roger S. (Box 68, Folder 2547)
  - Tracy, Uriah (Box 68, Folder 2547)
  - Traer, Charles S. (Box 68, Folder 2548)
  - Trager, G. L. (Box 68, Folder 2548)
  - Train, Abner L. (Box 68, Folder 2548)
  - Treadway, Morton Candee (Box 68, Folder 2549)
  - Treadwell, George Curtis (Box 68, Folder 2549)
  - Treadwell, John (Box 68, Folder 2549)
  - Treadwell, Levi Penfield (Box 68, Folder 2550)
  - Treadwell, Oliver F. (Box 68, Folder 2550)
  - Treat, Selan Burr (Box 68, Folder 2551)
  - Trevelyan, George M. (Box 68, Folder 2551)
  - Trinkhaus, J. P. (Box 68, Folder 2552)
  - Tripp, R. B. (Box 68, Folder 2553)
  - Trippe, Juan Terry (Box 68, Folder 2553)
  - Tritle, J. S. (Box 68, Folder 2553)
  - Troostwyk (Box 68, Folder 2554)
  - Trouche, Paul Edwin (Box 68, Folder 2554)
  - Trow, George William (Box 68, Folder 2554)
  - Trowbridge, Amasa (Box 68, Folder 2555)
  - Trowbridge, Edmund (Box 68, Folder 2555)
  - Trowbridge, Frank Dean (Box 68, Folder 2555)
  - Trowbridge, Henry (Box 68, Folder 2556)
  - Trowbridge, Henry, (Y. 1880) (Box 68, Folder 2556)
  - Trowbridge, William Petit (Box 68, Folder 2557)
  - Trowbridge, William Rutherford Hayes (Box 68, Folder 2558)
  - Troy, William (Box 68, Folder 2558)
  - Truman, Harry S. (Box 68, Folder 2559)
  - Trumbull, Benjamin (Box 68, Folder 2560)
  - Trumbull, Charles Edward (Box 68, Folder 2560)
  - Trumbull, David (Box 68, Folder 2560)
  - Trumbull, John (Y. 1767) (Box 68, Folder 2561)
  - Trumbull, Col. John (Box 68, Folder 2562-64)
  - Trumbull, Jonathan (Box 68, Folder 2565)
  - Trumbull, Joseph (Box 68, Folder 2566)
  - Trumbull, Richard Lindsay (Box 68, Folder 2566)
  - Trumbull, Stephen (Box 68, Folder 2566)
  - Trumbull, William (Box 68, Folder 2566)
  - Truxell, Thomas Ungrut (Box 69, Folder 2567)
  - Tryan, Earl H. (Y.1949) (Box 69, Folder 2567)
  - Tubbs, Chapin F. (Box 69, Folder 2568)
  - Tubbs, C. B. (Box 69, Folder 2568)
  - Tucker, John Dresser (Box 69, Folder 2568)
  - Tucker, John Randolph (Box 69, Folder 2568)
  - Tucker, Joshua Thomas (Box 69, Folder 2569)
  - Tully, James (Box 69, Folder 2569)
  - Tully, William (Box 69, Folder 2570)
  - Tuiss, Julius (Box 69, Folder 2571)
  - Tunney, Gene (Box 69, Folder 2571)
  - Turley (Box 69, Folder 2572)
  - Turner, Frank Browne (Box 69, Folder 2572)
  - Turner, Henry Holmes (Box 69, Folder 2572)
  - Turner, Jonathan Baldwin (Box 69, Folder 2572)
  - Turner, Lewis (Box 69, Folder 2573)
  - Turrell, Edgar Abel (Box 69, Folder 2573)
  - Tuttle, C. A. (Box 69, Folder 2573)